Guide to the Julie Braun-Vogelstein Collection, 1743-1971 AR 25034 / MF 473
Center for Jewish History, Publisher.
- Series III: Ludwig Vogelstein, undated, 1800s-1900s
  - (18/4): Ludwig Vogelstein Correspondence, Family Letters to Ludwig from Max, Hermann, Emmy Vogelstein, 1910-1933 (Box 17, Folder 125)
  - (18/5): Ludwig Vogelstein Correspondence, Letters from Hertha V. (Hermann's daughter) to Ludwig (Hermann's brother), 1923-1934 (Box 17, Folder 126)
  - (18/6): Ludwig Vogelstein Correspondence, Letters of Hermann V. to his brother Ludwig, 1911-1933 (Box 17, Folder 127)
  - (18/7): Ludwig Vogelstein, Correspondence Letters to LV's Psrents, 1891-1899 (Box 18, Folder 128)
  - (18/8): Ludwig Vogelstein, Correspondence Letters to LV's Parents, 1900-1906 (Box 18, Folder 129)
  - (18/9): Ludwig Vogelstein, Correspondence Letters to LV's Parents, 1907-1912 (Box 18, Folder 130)
  - (18/10): Ludwig Vogelstein, Correspondence Letters to LV's Parents, 1906-1920 (Box 18, Folder 131)
  - (18/11): Ludwig Vogelstein, Personal Documents of LV, 1880-1916 (Box 18, Folder 132)
  - (18/12): Ludwig Vogelstein, Excerpts from Letters of LV. (material for Julie's biogr. of her brother), ND (Box 18, Folder 133)
  - (18/13): Ludwig Vogelstein, Correspondence Letters of LV (Box 18, Folder 134)
  - (18/14): Ludwig Vogelstein, Correspondence Ludwig and Heinrich Braun (typewritten), 1916-1927 (Box 18, Folder 135)
  - (18/15): Ludwig Vogelstein, Heinrich Braun, 1920-1926 (Box 18, Folder 136)
  - (18/16): Ludwig Vogelstein, Speeches, 1916-1934 (Box 18, Folder 137)
- Series IV: Julie Braun-Vogelstein, undated, 1800s-1900s
  - Julie Braun Das Relief Third Version, pp.1-150. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Julie Braun Das Relief Third Version, pp. 151=322 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Julie Braun Das Relief Chap. IV-V, pp.480-800, c.1958 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Julie Braun Das Relief Chap. III pp.1-479, c.1958 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Julie Braun Das ReliefFourth Version 233pgs., c1958 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Julie Braun Das ReliefTyped Example1pp.115, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Julie Braun Das Relief Example 1, pp.116-231, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Julie Braun Das Relief Example 2, pp.1-115, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Julie Braun Das Relief Example 2 pp.11231, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Julie Braun Das Relief Example 3, pp.1-115, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Julie Braun Das Relief Example 3, pp.116-123, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Julie Braun Das Relief 4th Version pp.1-116, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Julie Braun Das Relief Chs. 1-5 pp.1-122, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Julie Braun Das Relief Chs.1-5 pp.123-243, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Julie Braun: Das Relief drafts (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Julie Braun: notes (Exkurse) and comments (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Julie Braun: comments about Excursus, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Julie Braun: Greek Relief Style 155 pp., n.d. (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Julie Braun: Greek Relief Style p.1-80, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Julie Braun: Greek Relief Style I. Version from Excursus XLVI, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Julie Braun: Greek Relief Style 1. Version, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Julie Braun: Das Relief Notes (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Julie Braun: Material for Das Relief, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Julie Braun: Material for Das Relief cont., n.d. (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Julie Braun: Material for Das Relief cont., n.d. (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Julie Braun: Material for Das Relief cont., n.d. (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Julie Braun: Photographs of Sculpture and Relief (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Julie Braun: Photographs of Sculpture and Relief Notes and Postcards Chapter 77 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Julie Braun: Photographs of Sculpture and Relief (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Julie Braun: Art History, Research Notes, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Julie Braun: Art History, Research Notes, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Julie Braun: Art History, Research Notes, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Julie Braun: Art History Notes on the Parthenon, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Julie Braun: Art History, Notes on th4e Parthenon Zehlendorf, c1923. (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Julie Braun: Notes on the Parthenon, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Julie Braun: Art History, Research Notes, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Julie Braun: Art History, Research Notes, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Julie Braun Notes on the Parthenon, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Julie Braun Art History Notes, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Julie Braun Art History Notes, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Julie Braun Art History Research Notes, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Julie Braun Art History Research Notes, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Julie Braun Art History Research Notes, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Julie Braun Art History Research Notes, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Julie Braun Art History Research Notes, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Julie Braun zur conishen Saeule, Rythm and Ornament Manuscrript, Correspondence, Photos, Periodicals (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Julie Braun Rhythm and Ornament, Manuscript, Pt. IV Photos, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Julie Braun Rhythm and Ornament, Manuscript, Pt. IV Photos, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Julie Braun Wesen und Erscheinungsformen der Klassik Manuscript pp. 1-112 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Julie Braun Wesen und Erscheinungsformen der Klassik Manuscript pp. 113-223 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Julie Braun Wesen und Erscheinungsformen der Klassik Manuscript pp. 226-334 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Julie Braun Wesen und Erscheinungsformen der Klassik Manuscript pp. 1-112, n.d. (Duplicate) (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Julie Braun Wesen und Erscheinungsformen der Klassik Manuscript pp. 113-273 (Duplicate) (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Julie Braun Wesen und Erscheinungsformen der Klassik Manuscript pp.224-330, n.d. (Duplicate) (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Julie Braun Abbilungsmaterial zur Klassik, inc. Photos, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - (9/1): Julie Braun Der Punkt im Leeren. (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - (9/2): Julie Braun General Manuscripts, various, 1933-1966 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - (9/3): Julie Braun Travaille Maman, Travaille and Poem byOtto Braun, c1913-1945 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - (9/4): Julie Braun Partial Manuscript of a book by Gertrude Oppenheimer sent to JBV Letters to JVB, 1939-1944 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - (9/5): Julie Braun Misc. Manuscripts, 1935-1943 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - (9/6): Julie Braun Misc. Manuscripts, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - (9/7): Julie Braun The Point in the Void, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - (9/8): Julie Braun Die mystische Erfahrung, The Mystical Experience 10 pp. each, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - (9/9): Julie Braun Thought and Thinking (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - (9/10): Julie Braun Recognition of Man die Wiedererkennung des Menschen (during the Battle of Britain), 1940 (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - (9/11): Julie Braun Manuscript: Ein Jahrelanges Gespraech, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - (9/12): Julie BraunManuscript: A Lasting Dialogue, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - (9/13): Julie Braun Reflexes of Truth: A conversation between Ouspensky and Gourdjieff (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - (9/14): Julie Braun Germany 1936-1941, pp.88-153, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - (9/15): Julie Braun Misc. Manuscripts, c1940's (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - (10/1): Julie Braun Artistic Form correction of Art the Image of the West, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - (10/2): Julie Braun Kuenstlerische Form, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - (10/3): Julie Braun Art History Manuscripts, 1934-1963 (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - (10/4): Julie Braun Art History Manuscripts, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - (10/5): Julie Braun Art History Manuscripts, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - (11): Julie Braun: Der Kreis des Lebens: Part I, 169 pp. (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - (11): Julie Braun: Der Kreis des Lebens: Part II 296 pp. (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - (11): Julie Braun: Der Kreis des Lebens:Part III, p.1-241 (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - (11): Julie Braun: Der Kreis des Lebens:Part III p.242-513 (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - (12/1): Julie Braun: proofs, manuscripts; Otto Braun; "Aus den nachgelassenen Schriften eines Fruehvollendeten";1920; 1969; Heinrich Braun;"Ein Leben fuer den Sozialismus"1916-1920, 1927., 1916-1969 (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - (12/2): Julie Braun: Manuscript Otto Braun, 1968. (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - (12/3): Julie Braun: Correspondence: Was niemals stirbt A-H, 1966-1970. (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - (12/4): Julie Braun: Correspondence: Was niemals stirbt I-Z, 1966-1967. (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - (12/5): Julie Braun: Reviews: Was niemals stirbt, 1966-1967. (Box 21, Folder 84)
  - Julie Braun: Reviews Heinrich Braun Clippngs, Pamphlets, 1927-1928. (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - Julie Braun: Correspondence, 1898-1959. (Box 21, Folder 86)
  - (13/1): Julie Braun: Heinrich Braun Biography manuscript Chapter XVI, pp.1 218., n.d. (Box 21, Folder 87)
  - (13/2): Julie Braun: Heinrich Braun Biography manuscript Chapter XVII pp.1-288., n.d. (Box 21, Folder 88)
  - (13/3): Julie Braun: Heinrich Braun Biography manuscript Chapter XVIII pp.1-237., n.d. (Box 21, Folder 89)
  - (13/4): Julie Braun: Heinrich Braun Biography introduction pp.1-5, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 90)
  - (14/1): Julie Braun Home and Parents Autobiography Preface, Chapter I manuscript and corrections English Translation Correspondence with Translator, 1960-1962 (Box 22, Folder 91)
  - (14/2): Julie Braun Home and Parents Autobiography chapters 2-4 manuscript and corrections to English Translatioon Correspomndemce with translator, c1960--1962 (Box 22, Folder 92)
  - (14/3): Julie Braun Home and Parents Autobiography chapters 5-7 correspondence and corrections to English translation, c 1960-1962 (Box 22, Folder 93)
  - (14/4): Julie Braun Home and Parents Autobiography chapters 8-9 epilogue Corrections relating to English translatioon. (Box 22, Folder 94)
  - (14/5): Julie Braun Mein Bruder Ludwig manuscript, English translation, Part 2 Introdction chapters 1-6 pp. 1-115, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 95)
  - (14/6): Julie Braun Mein Bruder Ludwig English Translation Part 2 Chapters VII- XII pp.116-253 Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 96)
  - (15/1): Julie Braun Correspondence, personal re: Ellis Island Internment, 1941-1943 (Box 22, Folder 97)
  - (15/2): Julie Braun Correspondence, official re: Ellis Island Internment, 1937-1943 (Box 22, Folder 98)
  - (15/3): Julie Braun Correspondence and papers re: Ellis Island Internment of Hasso von Seebach, foster son of JBV (Box 22, Folder 99)
  - (15/4): Julie Braun Correspondence letters to JVB from various people re: money and immigration, 1938-1939 (Box 22, Folder 100)
  - (15/5): Julie Braun; Papers re: JVB's trip abroad 1938; legal aspects of her absence and re-entry to USA; correspondence and legal documents re: estate of Ludwing Braun, 1937-1938 (Box 22, Folder 101)
  - (15/6): Julie Braun JVB's Passports and Report cards from Univ. of Berlin unidentified phograph of 2 children, 1919-1959 (Box 22, Folder 102)
  - (15/7): Julie Braun Cancelled Checks + Stubs Natalie Freiberger, 1965; 1971 (Box 22, Folder 103)
  - (15/8): Julie Braun Financial Correspondence: Health Insurance, Pension and Restitution Natalie Freiberger, 1951-1966 (Box 22, Folder 104)
  - (15/9): Julie Braun Employees' Social Security and Unemployment Insurance, 1959-1971 (Box 22, Folder 105)
  - (15/10): Julie Braun Correspondence re. her Will, 1959-1969 (Box 22, Folder 106)
  - (15/11): Julie Braun Correspondence:. Business and Publishing A-K, 1953-1964 (Box 22, Folder 107)
  - (15/12): Julie Braun Correspondence:Publishing L-Z, 1951-1965 (Box 22, Folder 108)
  - (15/13): Julie Braun Correspondence with Bundesarchiv freier Deutscher Hochstift, Frankfurter Goethe Museum, 1953-1969 (Box 22, Folder 109)
  - (16/1): Julie Braun Correspondence: mostly Henry Ormond, Rechtsanwalt (lawyer), 1934-1966 (Box 22, Folder 110)
  - (16/2): Julie Braun Correspondence re. Estate of Ludwig V. and Trust Fund, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 111)
  - (16/3): Julie Braun Correspondence: Business Theodore and Hans Vogelstein, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 112)
  - (16/4): Julie Braun Correspondence:Dresdner Bank, 1935 36 (Box 22, Folder 113)
  - (16/5): Julie Braun Correspondence re. Estate, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 114)
  - (16/6): Julie Braun Correspondence + Business papers, 1924-1939 (Box 22, Folder 115)
  - (16/7): Julie Braun Business papers, 1934-1941 (Box 22, Folder 116)
  - (16/8): Julie Braun Dresdner Bank, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 117)
  - (16/9): Julie Braun Letters to Hans Vogelstein re. Family Business Matters, 1934; 1958 (Box 22, Folder 118)
  - (17/1): Julie Braun Drawings by JVB, 1898-1899 (Box 22, Folder 119)
  - (17/2): Julie Braun Excerpts from Diaries + 1 letter, 1938; 1943-1944; 1951 (Box 22, Folder 120)
  - (17/3): Julie Braun Misc. Drawings, Pictures, n.d. c1950's (Box 22, Folder 121)
  - (17/4): Julie Braun; Photographs; Classical Reliefs; n.d.; c1950,s; Duplicates: JVB, Natural Scenes; n.d., n.d., ca.1950s (Box 22, Folder 122)
  - (18): Julie Braun Art History Research Notes, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 123)
  - (18): Julie Braun Art History Research Notes, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 124)
  - (18): Julie Braun Art History Research Notes, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 125)
  - (18): Julie Braun Art History Research Notes, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 126)
  - (18): Julie Braun Art History Research Notes, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 127)
  - (18): Julie Braun Art History Research Notes, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 128)
  - (18): Julie Braun Art History Research Notes, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 129)
  - (18): Julie Braun Art History Research Notes, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 130)
  - (18): Julie Braun Art History Research Notes and Bibliography, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 131)
  - (19): Julie Braun Art History Research Notes, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 132)
  - (19): Julie Braun Art History Research Notes, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 133)
  - (19): Julie Braun Art History Research Notes, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 134)
  - (19): Julie Braun Art History Research Notes, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 135)
  - (19): Julie Braun Art History Research Notes and Bibliographical Notes, 1913; 1927, c1956 (Box 23, Folder 136)
  - (19): Julie Braun Art History Research Notes and Bibliographical Notes (Box 23, Folder 137)
  - (20/1): Julie Braun Lilly Braun's Liuebes Briefe der Marquise, English TranslationChapters1-3 pp.1-112, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 138)
  - (20/2): Julie Braun Lilly Braun's Liuebes Briefe der Marquise, English Translation Chapters 4-6 pp.113-207, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 139)
  - (20/3): Julie Braun Lilly Braun's Liuebes Briefe der Marquise, English Translation Chapters 7-8 pp. 208=312, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 140)
  - (20/4): Julie Braun Correspondence: Ignatz + Ida Braun, 1880-1899. (Box 23, Folder 141)
  - (20/5): Julie Braun Correspondence Ignatz + Ida Braun, 1882-1890 (Box 23, Folder 142)
  - (20/6): Julie Braun Correspondence Ignatz + Ida Braun, 1880-1891 (Box 23, Folder 143)
  - (20/7): Julie Braun Correspondence Ignatz + Ida Braun, 1880-1898 (Box 23, Folder 144)
  - (21/1): Julie Braun The Middle East by William Haas Manuscript, 16 pp. Introduction, 20 pp Outline for The Structure of Western and Eastern Mind. (Box 23, Folder 145)
  - (21/2): Julie Braun ThebLanguage of Silence Copy of Manuscript by William Haas 20 pp., n.d. (Box 23, Folder 146)
  - (21/3): Julie Braun Das Werden der Formen des Geistes by William Haas Manuscript pp.21-68, with Notes (Box 23, Folder 147)
  - (21/4): Julie Braun The Battle of Awnd by Willis Bandler 123 pages (Box 24, Folder 148)
  - (21/5): Julie Braun Herta Vogelstein manuscripts, 1922,1957 (Box 24, Folder 149)
  - (21/6): Julie Braun Misc. Articles, Poetry H. Fries, 1934; 1959-1964 (Box 24, Folder 150)
  - (21/7): Julie Braun Articles on misc.subjects, 1958, 1963-1970 (Box 24, Folder 151)
  - (21/8): Julie Braun Articles, misc. subjects, c1964-1971 (Box 24, Folder 152)
  - (21/9): Julie Braun Articles, misc. subjects, 1959-1967 (Box 24, Folder 153)
  - (21/10): Julie Braun Articles by Ernst Simon, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 154)
  - (21/11): Julie Braun Articles on Archaeology, 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 155)
  - (21/12): Julie Braun Juden in Theresienstadt by Oberst Prochnik, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 156)
  - (21/13): Julie Braun Dr. Ulrich Noack Correspondence, 1937 (Box 24, Folder 157)
  - (21/14): Julie Braun Wyllis Bandler miscellaneoius manuscripts, 1951-1967 (Box 24, Folder 158)
  - (22/1): Julie Braun Abschrift (copy) letters by F. Thimme, 1885-1914, 1933-1934 (Box 24, Folder 159)
  - (22/2): Julie Braun Photocopies of letters by F. Thimme to H. Braun, 1933-1938 (Box 24, Folder 160)
  - (22/3): Julie Braun Photocopies of letters by F. Thimme to H. Braun, 1918-1939 (Box 24, Folder 161)
  - (23): Julie Braun Translations Poetry, German to Engl., n.d. (Box 24, Folder 162)
  - (23): Julie Braun Translations,`Poetry, Engl. to German, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 163)
  - (23): Julie Braun Tranlations of Greek Poetry to German, 1956-1958 (Box 24, Folder 164)
  - (23): Julie Braun Poetry,Translations English and German, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 165)
  - (23/5): Julie Braun Art News Clippings+ Phographs, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 166)
  - (23/6): Julie Braun Stenographische Berichte ueber die Verhandlungen des Reichstags, 1881; 1887 (Box 24, Folder 167)
  - (23/7): Julie Braun Speech by Merton Notes-Jastrow, 1926 (Box 24, Folder 168)
  - (23/8): Julie Braun Ernst Laas material, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 169)
  - (23/9): Julie BraunPamphlets, Newspaper Clippings, Journals, 1921-1959 (Box 24, Folder 170)
  - (23/10): Julie Braun Manuscript, partial, c1933-1937 (Box 24, Folder 171)
  - (23/11): Julie Braun Art, Reproductions, Photos, c1964 (Box 24, Folder 172)
  - (23/12): Julie Braun Miscellaneous, inc.Photos, 1919-c; 1957 (Box 24, Folder 173)
  - (23/13) Julie BraunUnidentified Miscellaneous, 1935-1951 (Box 24, Folder 174)
  - (23/1): Julie Braun HillebrandQuotebook, 1900-1936; 1939 (Box 24, Folder 175)
  - (24/1): Julie Braun Correspondence Otto Heinich Braun, 1913-1916 (Box 24, Folder 176)
  - (24/2): Julie Braun Poetry of Otto Braun German+English, nd (Box 24, Folder 177)
  - Julie Braun Letters to JVB about Lily Braun's Lebensbildm, 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 178)
  - Julie Braun Misc. papers, 1903; 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 179)
  - Julie Braun Copy of letter from Kautsky to JBV, 1927 (Box 24, Folder 180)
  - Julie Braun Letters to Julie+ Heinrich Braun, 1921-1924 (Box 24, Folder 181)
  - Julie Braun Misc. Notes, Clippings, 1895; 1919; 1947-1961 (Box 24, Folder 182)
  - Julie Braun Heinich Braun Biography Manuscript VII, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 183)
  - Julie Braun Heinich Braun Correspondence interview re. Acauaintance w. Freud, 1894-1959 (Box 25, Folder 184)
  - Julie Braun Heinich Braun Correspondence re. HB, 1931-1932 (Box 25, Folder 185)
  - Julie Braun Heinich Braun Condolence letters on the Death of HB, 1927 (Box 25, Folder 186)
  - Julie Braun Pamphlets, misc., 1927 (Box 25, Folder 187)
  - Julie Braun Heinich Braun Newspaper Clippings re. HB's Death, 1927 (Box 25, Folder 188)
  - (25/1): Julie Braun Correspondence Letters to and from Family, 1900-1957 (Box 25, Folder 189)
  - (25/2): Julie Braun Correspondence, Family Letters of Rosa Vogelstein, Mocity K., Max, Hans, Ruth, 1912-1960 (Box 25, Folder 190)
  - (25/3): Julie Braun Auszuege (excerpts) Family Julie to parents, Ludwig,Lily, Otto,Lily and Otto to Julie, 1910-1917 (Box 25, Folder 191)
  - (25/4): Julie Braun; Correspondence; Mr + Mrs Warren Vogel- stein, 1961 _1970; 2-way corespondence w.Hans + Ruth Vogelstein; 1958-1960, 1958-1970 (Box 25, Folder 192)
  - (25/5): Julie Braun correspondenceletters from Herta V., 1959-1962 (Box 25, Folder 193)
  - (25/6): Julie Braun correspondence from the Max Vogelsteins (Max, Inge, Hermann), 1967-1970 (Box 25, Folder 194)
  - (25/7): Julie Braun correspondence Max, Inge, Hermann, 1959-1966 (Box 25, Folder 195)
  - (25/8): Julie Braun correspondence Theodore Vogelstein, 1899 -1957 (Box 25, Folder 196)
  - (25/9): Julie Braun correspondence, Ludwig V., 1919; family financial problems, 1932-1934 (Box 25, Folder 197)
  - (25/10): Julie Braun correspondence Theodore, inc. musical score, 1888-1960 (Box 25, Folder 198)
  - (25/11): Julie Braun correspondence misc. about Hermann and Warren Vogelstein, 1911-1962 (Box 25, Folder 199)
  - (25/12): Julie Braun On the Jewish Problem by Theodore Vogelstein, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 200)
  - (25/13): Julie Braun Peace in European and Americqn Good Will by Theodore Vogelstein (Box 25, Folder 201)
  - (26/1): Julie Braun Correspondence to JVB, 1909-1969 (Box 25, Folder 202)
  - (26/2): Julie Braun Correspondence from William Haas, 1941 -1956 (Box 25, Folder 203)
  - (26/3): Julie Braun Correspondence Kurt Paesler Lusch Kowko (friend of Otto Braun), 1919-1939 (Box 25, Folder 204)
  - (26/4): Julie Braun Correspondence Misc. A-K, 1949-1958 (Box 25, Folder 205)
  - (26/5): Julie Braun Corrrespondence Misc. L-Z, 1951-1952 (Box 25, Folder 206)
  - (26/6): Julie Braun Correspondence and clippings re JVB's book Ionic Columns, 1912-1945 (Box 26, Folder 207)
  - (26/7): Julie Braun Reviews of JVB's work, Cprrespondence, Clippings, 1951-1958 (Box 26, Folder 208)
  - (26/8): Julie Braun Correspondence, clippings re lily Braun, Otto, Heinrich, 1923 (Box 26, Folder 209)
  - (27/1): Julie Braun Correspondence, Excerpts Research Notes, 1920-1938+B687 (Box 26, Folder 210)
  - (27/2): Julie Braun Correspondence, Excerpts Research Notes, 1928-1934 (Box 26, Folder 211)
  - (27/3): Julie Braun Correspondence, Excerpts Research Notes, 1902-1938 (Box 26, Folder 212)
  - (27/4): Julie Braun Correspondence, Excerpts Research Notes, 1920-1934 (Box 26, Folder 213)
  - (27/5): Julie Braun Auszuege aus Buechern (excerpts from books) Notes on the middle ages, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 214)
  - (27/6): Julie Braun William Haas, Felix Adler-JBV, Gespraeche William Haas, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 215)
  - (27/7): Julie Braun Notes, 1920 (Box 26, Folder 216)
  - (27/8): Julie Braun Clippings, 1933; 1963-1970 (Box 26, Folder 217)
  - (27/9): Julie Braun Correspondence Notes Clippings, 1963-1971 (Box 26, Folder 218)
  - (27/10): Julie Braun Correspondence Notes Clippings, 1923-1960 (Box 26, Folder 219)
  - (27/11): Julie Braun Correspondence, papers, 1952-1956 (Box 26, Folder 220)
  - (27/12): Julie Braun Unidentified Correspondence Lists, 1935-1971 (Box 26, Folder 221)
  - (28/1): Julie Braun Photographs and Postcards, China, c1948 (Box 26, Folder 222)
  - (28/2): Julie Braun Curt Bley manuscript on A von Trott G E Collins, 7 pp. tw List of German Families in Plot to kill Hitler, 17 pp. tw, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 223)
  - (28/3): Julie Braun Correspondence Werner von Trott, 1935-1936 (Box 26, Folder 224)
  - (28/4): Julie Braun Manuscript, Three Germans of the Resistance, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 225)
  - (28/5): Julie Braun Manuscript, Adam von Troot, no author specified, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 226)
  - (28/6): Julie Braun Notes on Adam von Trott by G E Collins, on Proletarische Position. and other Manusc. by Adam von Trott, 1946-1947 (Box 26, Folder 227)
  - (28/7): Julie Braun Manuscript, Articles, Correspondence, 1952-1963 (Box 26, Folder 228)
  - (28/8): Julie Braun List of executed in 1944 (Box 26, Folder 229)
  - (28/9): Julie Braun Correspondence, Articles, Clippings, 1944-1947 (Box 26, Folder 230)
  - (28/10): Julie Braun Correspondence, Werner von Trott, 1946-1952 (Box 26, Folder 231)
  - (28/11): Julie Braun Correspondence, Adam von Trott, 1935-1938 (Box 26, Folder 232)
  - (28/12): Julie Braun Correspondence, Adam von Trott, 1938-1940 (Box 26, Folder 233)
  - (28/13): Julie Braun Correspondence, Clarita von Trott (Adam's wife), 1946-1952 (Box 26, Folder 234)
  - (28/14): Julie Braun Correspondence, Eleanor von Trott, 1936-1947 (Box 26, Folder 235)
  - (28/15): Julie Braun Correspondence, Heinrich von Troff to Martha and JVB, 1945-1948; 1964 (Box 26, Folder 236)
  - (28/16): Julie Braun Correspondence, Diana Hopkinson, 1938-1946 (Box 26, Folder 237)
  - (29/1): Julie Braun Adam von Trott material, clippings, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 238)